portillos.com 2015-12-04

# Privacy Statement | Portillo's

Effective 3/24/15

Dear Customer,

The Portillo Restaurant Group* is concerned about protecting your privacy and the safety of all our Web site visitors. Before you use The Portillo Restaurant Group Web site, submit any personal information, apply for a job or place an order through Portillo’s E-store, please read this message. 

**A Special Note for Parents**  
The Portillo Restaurant Group believes that parents and guardians should supervise their children's online activities and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers that help provide a child-friendly online environment. These tools can also prevent children from disclosing online their name, address, and other personal information without your permission.  We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen.  Parents or guardians with questions about our practices related to children’s online privacy may contact us at [guestservices@portillos.com](mailto:guestservices@portillos.com).

**What This Site Contains**  
Our Web site contains information about the various concepts within The Portillo Restaurant Group, including Portillo's Hot Dogs, Barnelli’s Pasta Bowl and Portillo's Home Kitchen.  Check out the locations nearest you. You can also obtain information about working for Portillo's! When visiting our Web site, don’t forget to browse in our E-Store and order some favorite items to ship to your friends. Be sure to visit us in person to discover the great food and quality service that put Portillo’s in a class by itself!

**Information Collected**  
The Portillo Restaurant Group is very sensitive to the privacy concerns of the visitors to its Web site. As a general policy, no personal information is collected automatically from visitors to our Web site.  Personal information is collected only when voluntarily submitted.  Such voluntary submissions include emails sent to us, registration for a mailing list, applying for a job with us, placement of an order through Portillo’s E-store and creation of an account on our Web site. The type of personal information we may collect when submitted by you includes:

  * Contact information, such as your name, email address, postal address and telephone number 

  * The name, birth date, email address, postal address and telephone number you submit for anyone else

  * Your birth date

  * Educational background, employment history and other information relevant to any job(s) for which you apply 

  * Payment information (such as credit card information, financial account information and billing address)

  * Your order history from our E-Store

  * Other personal information you may provide 

A visitor who creates an account on our Web site may login to his or her account to edit the information provided.

Certain non-personal information of visitors is recorded through the standard operation of The Portillo Restaurant Group's Internet servers.  Information tracked includes the type of operating system in use (e.g., Macintosh, Windows) and the type of browser being used by the visitor (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer).

**E-Store Provisions**  
_Ordering Information We Collect Online for Portillo's E-Store_  
When a customer places an order online, we collect information associated with the transaction. This information includes the customer's name, mailing address, products ordered, shipping addresses, and credit card information. We ask for this information so that we may fulfill the order. The information is stored on our customer file in a secure environment. Terms for information collection within the E-store are governed by the E-store Provisions. Please read these terms before shopping at Portillo's E-store.

When a customer places an online order, we will send an e-mail confirmation of the order and an email with order tracking information. We will also send an email to confirm phone orders where email addresses have been provided.  We also may occasionally send an e-mail featuring a special promotion or product that may be of interest to our customers.  In addition, when a customer places an order online, we add the customer's name and address to our mailing list.  If a customer does not wish to receive our mailings or promotional materials, he or she can send us an e-mail at [guestservices@portillos.com](mailto:guestservices@portillos.com) requesting to be removed from our mailing list, or send the mailing label to the following address:     
        The Portillo Restaurant Group  
        Attn:  Guest Services  
        2001 Spring Road, Suite 500  
        Oak Brook, IL 60523    

**Use of Cookies**  
When you visit our Web site, we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "Cookie" and will help us in several ways.  For example, Cookies allow us to tailor our Web site to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet browsers, you can erase Cookies from your computer hard drive, block all Cookies, or receive a warning before a Cookie is stored.  Please be aware, however, that without cookies, you may not be able to use all of the features of our Site.  We may also utilize a  “web beacon," also known as an Internet tag, pixel tag or clear GIF, which links web pages to web servers and their cookies and may be used to transmit information collected through cookies back to a web server. Through these automated collection methods, we obtain "clickstream data," which is a log of content on which a visitor clicks while browsing a website. As the visitor clicks through the website, a record of the action may be collected and stored.  Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.  

If you use Site features operated by third-party social networking services (such as Facebook), we may receive information you have made available to those services, including the geographic location of your mobile device and other information about you (such as your name, email address, gender, physical location, social media profile URL, personal website URL, biographical information, birthday, photo, list of devices, education history, work history, hometown, interests, current city, political views, favorite athlete and teams, relationship status and information, religion, name of significant other, and certain security settings information) and your contacts on those services. Some of these social networking services allow you to push content from our Sites to your contacts or to pull information about your contacts so you can connect with them on our Sites. Some of these services also will facilitate your registration for our Sites or enhance or personalize your experience on our Sites. You should make sure you understand the information your third-party social networking services may make available to our Sites. We may use and disclose the personal information we receive on our Sites through third-party social networking services as described in this Privacy Statement.

**How We Use the Information Collected**  
Unless otherwise disclosed during the collection or required by law, personal information that may be collected in connection with a visit to this site is retained by The Portillo Restaurant Group.  We may use the information collected through the Web site for any of the following purposes:

  * To create and manage your account;

  * To process and collect payments from you for your E-Store purchases;

  * To offer you products and services;

  * To send you information you request;

  * To manage and communicate with you in relation to an application for employment you submit to us and to contact you about opportunities with The Portillo Restaurant Group;

  * To send information to others at your request 

  * To communicate with you about special offers, promotions, events, sweepstakes or surveys;

  * To conduct marketing analysis to improve our products and services and our Web site;

  * To review the number of visitors to our Web site;

  * To provide an enhanced online experience for visitors to our Web site; and

  * To comply with all applicable laws and requirements and policies of The Portillo Restaurant Group.

We may use third-party web analytics services that employ technologies such as cookies, web server logs and web beacons to help us analyze how visitors use our Web site. The information collected is disclosed to these third-party providers, who use the information to evaluate use of our Site.  For more information, or to learn how to opt out, please visit www.google.com/analytics.  We may also use the information we obtain from you in other ways, for which we provide specific notice at the time of collection.

**Advertising Based on Interests**  
We may collect information on our Web site about your online activities for use in providing you with advertising about products and services tailored to your individual interests. 

You may see certain ads on other Web sites based on your visits to our Web site because we participate in an advertising network administered by a third-party vendor. Ad networks allow us to target our messaging to users through demographics and interests. These networks track your online activities over time by collecting information through automated means, including through the use of cookies, web server logs and web beacons. The networks use this information to show you advertisements that are tailored to your individual interests. The information our ad network vendor collects include information about your visits to Web sites that participate in the vendor’s advertising networks, such as the pages or advertisements you view and the actions you take on the Web sites. This data collection takes place both on our Web site and on third-party websites that participate in the ad network. This process also helps us track the effectiveness of our marketing efforts. To learn more about how to opt out of ad network advertising, please visit: http://www.aboutads.info/choices/.

**Information We Share**  
The Portillo Restaurant Group does not sell information gathered about you on our Web site to third parties.  Except as described in this Privacy Statement, we do not share personal information gathered about you. We share personal information with third parties who perform services on our behalf in accordance with our instructions.  We may also share information we obtain from you with our affiliates.  

In addition, we may disclose information about you when required to do so by law, regulation or legal process (such as court order or subpoena), in response to requests by government agencies or law enforcement personnel, or in connection with an investigation into suspected criminal activity.  We may also disclose information when we believe disclosure is necessary to prevent harm.

**How We Protect the Information you Provide**  
The Portillo Restaurant Group utilizes administrative, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect the personal information you provide from accidental, unauthorized or unlawful access, alteration, disclosure, use, destruction or loss.   

**California Residents**  
Subject to certain limitations under California Civil Code § 1798.83, California residents may request a list of certain categories of personal information we have disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year, and for the identity of those third parties.  California residents may contact us at [guestservices@portillos.com](mailto:guestservices@portillos.com) or by mail to The Portillo Restaurant Group, 2001 Spring Road, Suite 500, Oak Brook, IL 60523, to make such a request.  

**Links to Other Sites**  
Our Web site may contain links to other Web sites that are operated by companies not affiliated with The Portillo Restaurant Group.  The Portillo Restaurant Group is not responsible for the content or privacy practices on any these non-Portillo sites.  If you are accessing these non-Portillo sites, we strongly encourage you to review the privacy policy and practices associated with those sites.  

**Acceptance of Privacy Statement**  
Thank you for reading our Privacy Statement. We hope you have a better understanding of our commitment to safeguarding online privacy. If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Statement or Terms and Conditions, please contact us using one of the following methods:

        Email:  [guestservices@portillos.com](mailto:guestservices@portillos.com)

        Mail:    The Portillo Restaurant Group  
                    2001 Spring Road, Suite 500  
                    Oak Brook, IL 60523

        Phone: (630) 954-3773 or (855) 483-0440  

Your access and use of this site is subject to the above Privacy Statement, the Web site’s Terms and Conditions and all applicable laws. By accessing and browsing this site, you accept, without limitation or qualification, these Terms and Conditions. The Portillo Restaurant Group may at any time revise its Privacy Statement and the Terms and Conditions, and the revised versions will be posted on this Web site. You are bound by any such revisions and should therefore periodically visit this page to review the then current Privacy Statement and our Terms and Conditions.

_*Refers collectively to Portillo’s Hot Dogs, LLC and its subsidiaries, Portillo’s of Arizona, LLC and Portillo’s Hot Dogs of Indiana, LLC, Portillo’s Food Service, LLC and Golden Dogs, LLC._

Revised 3/24/15
